
Snowboarding is all around us. You've heard about it from your friends, from the pro atheletes competing in the X-Games, the Olympics. Surely you've seen in those goPro videos. You finally find the courage in you and catch the first chairlift to the top of the mountain.  As you near the top, panic fills your body and it's time to stand up and ride of the lift.  Just like that, the fear of your first lift ride turns into passion: passion for snowboarding.
The day ended way too quick, and you can't wait to get back up there.  As you're headign back home, the search for your own snowboard has already begun. "Buy Snowboard" search querry brings up all these terms start to pop-up: types of snowboards, different sizes, shape, flex, bindings. The joy quickly fades and turns into something completely unfamiliar to a regular Joe.
Enter the unknown:
This interactive guide will help you with the initial investment into your snowboarding future.